One of the things I tell young
men, well young women as well.
But the young men really need
to hear this more I think is
that you should be a monster,
You know, because everyone says,
well, you should be harmless, virtuous.
You shouldn't do anyone any harm.
You should your competitive instinct.
You shouldn't try to win.
You know, you you don't
wanna be too aggressive.
If you don't wanna
be too assertive.
If you wanna take a back seat
and all of those. Like, no.
Wrong, you should
be a monster,
an absolute monster and then you
should learn how to control it.
Being aggressive. That means
you are ready to attack.
As I always point out, this
doesn't mean you walk around with
your chest puff out ready to bang
heads with everyone around you.
It doesn't mean you confront
people physically or mentally
head on without a tactically
superior plan. No.
What it does mean is that you
are going to get after it.
You going to move fast. You
are going to think fast.
You are going to out think
and out maneuver the enemy.
If I think the enemy is going to attack
me, I'm going to attack them first.
If I think they are going to
seize a piece of terrain,
I am gonna be there
waiting for them.
If I think the enemy is going to flank
me too late, I'm already flanking them.
I view aggression as a buyer in your
mind that says, I am going to win.
I I'm am going to battle and
I'm am going to fight and I'm
going to use every tool
I have to crush my me.
And that is what aggression is to me
the unstoppable fighting spirit.
The drive, the burning is desire
to achieve mission success
using every possible tool,
asset, and strategy,
and tactic to bring up out
victory. It is the will to win.
And if that kind of internal relentless
aggression is your you default alone.
You will win. You think that
your competitors are better than
you that somebody who's gonna take
your position. Turn up the game.
Step off to the next level,
take practice boy through.
Put more hours here, put more
time in challenge yourself to
reach another mountain. Challenge
yourself to feature that is.
Challenge yourself to be a star.
Challenge yourself to win the chat.
Your haters want you
to fake. Right down,
make the decision that
you won't give up,
make the decision that you
won't give in. My why?
This pushes me to
another level.
It pushes me to doing things
that I didn't know I can do.
It pushes me to be great. Greatness
has not only talked about.
It's about the work
that you put in.